(Leonard:)The math is all there.
(Leonard:)-It's not real.
-Yes, it is.
(Sheldon:)Look.
It is scientifically impossible
(Sheldon:)for a person to tip a cow.
(Sheldon:)Even you, with your stocky build
(Sheldon:)and lumberjack shoulders,
you couldn't do it.
(Raj:)It's horrible. Why would you push
a cow over? They're sacred.
(Penny:)Oh, stop it.
(Penny:)I've seen you eat,
like, a million hamburgers.
(Raj:)Hey, an animal can be both
sacred and delicious.
Lock, I'm telling you
I've done it, okay?
(Penny:)I clearly remember
the cow standing up
(Penny:)and then the cow on its side.
(Leonard:)Were you drunk?
(Penny:)I was 16 in Nebraska.
What do you think?
(Leonard:)I think you're the one who fell over.
(Penny:)That would explain why the sky
was also on its side.
(Raj:)-Hey.
-Howard.
(Penny:)real or not?
I'm going to say... not.
(Howard:)That's just based on me
trying to roll
(Howard:)my mom over
when she's snoring.
(Howard:)Speaking of that big side of beef,
(Howard:)she's invited all of you
to Thanksgiving at her house.
(Howard:)Mmm.
(Sheldon:)You know, I've been told
that a bald refusal
(Sheldon:)of an invitation is rude
and one must instead
(Sheldon:)offer up a polite excuse, so...
(Sheldon:)I'd love to go, but, unfortunately,
(Sheldon:)that sounds awful.
(Howard:)Come on, it'll be fun.
(Penny:)We were actually
going to do it here.
(Howard:)Please?
Bernadette's bringing her dad,
because her mom's out of town,
(Howard:)and I never have anything
to say to that guy.
(Sheldon:)Since you put it that way,
I'd love to go,
(Sheldon:)but that sounds even more awful.
(Leonard:)It'd actually be nice to not hear
(Leonard:)Sheldon complain
about my cooking all day.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me,
(Sheldon:)but every year
you prepare a terrible meal
(Sheldon:)and every year I criticize it.
(Sheldon:)Do our traditions
mean nothing to you?
(Leonard:)-I want to go.
-Yeah, me, too.
(Raj:)-I'm in.
-Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)Fine, I'll go.
(Sheldon:)But if her food is delicious,
Thanksgiving is ruined,
(Sheldon:)and it's on you.
I (THEME SONG PLAYS) I